https://leemfiltration.com/privacy-policy

Leem Model VLD
LEEM Model TB (Tube Filter)
Leem Model VLD
LEEM Model TB (Tube Filter)
Privacy Policy
LEEM Filtration Inc. respects the privacy of its website visitors and adheres to best practices, applicable U.S. federal laws, and acknowledges the European Union General Data Protection Regulation implementation.
LEEM Filtration, Inc., our website address is http://leemfiltration.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Contact forms
We collect the data provided by you. We store that information for marketing purposes; we do not share that information.
Cookies
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me,” your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g., videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Who we share your data with
We may from time to time share your date with our parent company, North American Filter, and its subsidiaries for marketing purposes.
How long we retain your data
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
For GDPR requests, please contact Stacey Painter at spainter@nafilter.com
Additional information
Third parties
This site may be using a third-party cloud storage to store backups of its audit logs where personal information is collected.
Additional data
This site creates and stores an activity log that captures the IP address, username, email address and tracks user activity (like when a user makes a purchase). Information will be stored locally for 30 days and remotely for one year. Information on remote logs cannot be cleared for security purposes.
Call Us
TEL:  201.236.4833
Links
HOMEABOUTPRODUCTSCONTACT
Meet Us
LEEM FILTRATION25 Arrow Road RoadRamsey, New Jersey 07446info@leemfiltration.com
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
X
